Terrell C. Lombardi

Schmidtstrasse 30 | D-65385 Rüdesheim am Rhein +49 151 65227520 tcl71771@yahoo.com www.linkedin.com/in/terry-c-lombardi/



Business analyst

Solve Complex Business Problems and Fueling Revenue Growth.

Qualification profile

Functional and cost-oriented project manager. Agile manager of interdisciplinary and intercultural specialists. Innovative and analytical process optimizer and potential dehusator. Passionate and empathetic project specialist with assertive negotiation skills. Decisive requirements and stakeholder manager.

Competences and skills

- Statistical and predictive analytics
- Create detailed reports describing the company's current performance, goals, resources, and performance gaps
- Analyze market trends and uncover growth opportunities
- Create statistical data visualizations through company data

Training

Full-stack web development 05/2021 – 09/2021 CareerSelectric

General Liberal Arts AA 2004 Pensacola Junior College, Pensacola, FL

Selection of projects

- Developed a strategic business and marketing plan that effectively turned a loss of \$40t per month into a profit of \$60t per month.
- Effective communication of the business world to help companies collaborate to double the city's trade.

Professional career

Managing Owner Marketing Solid Basics, LLC Mebane, NC 10/2014 - 06/2016

Strategic and operational management and responsibility for \$1.8 million in revenue. Determination of optimization and development opportunities as well as their implementation for value preservation. Establishment and further development of an efficient organization that is appropriate to the business model and the volume. Establishment and maintenance of active business relationships with operational partners and target contacts. Implementation of a future-oriented corporate strategy. Development and implementation of sales-increasing and innovative measures.

- Significant increase in sales of approximately \$50T per month
- Development of the community outreach program that meets the needs of the city
- Development and implementation of an annual business plan and customer service manual

Branch Manager / Vice President / Bank official 1 SunTrust Bank HillSborough, NC

7/2012 - 10/2014

Management of sales activities in the store under the power of attorney. Daily coordination and controls. Responsibility and development of a team of up to 15 employees. Fast, competent and friendly handling of all customer concerns. Administration, opening and administration of customers. Monitoring and target achievement. Customer acquisition and customer service. Area responsibility of the insurance business.

• Establishment of the branch as the most profitable branch in the region

TerrUlna C. Lombardi | Side 2

Cash Research Officer Apria Healthcare, Inc. Morrisville, NC 11/2008 - 07/2012

Coordination and clarification of open items. Ordering and posting of incoming payments and clarification of any payment differences. Management of credit checks and monitoring of the credit limit. Contact person for domestic and foreign customers, as well as interface function to internal departments for customer inquiries. Processing of correspondence with debt collection agencies and insolvency administrators as well as preparation of the summary statement.

- Execution of over 350 transactions per hour with a mandatory minimum number of transactions of 110 transactions per hour
- Successful implementation of new transaction processing strategies
- Processing all medical claims from all 50 states and Federal Medicare as the only person in the company

Additional experience

Freelance programmer | Various customers

Various administrative positions | Mega Force Sanford / Brickcity Community Church Sanford / Lee County Sanford Tax Administration

Website Moderator/Editor | Pensacola

Operations Manager | CompUSA Ft Walton Beach

Managing Director | CyberZone Pensacola

New and used car manager - Financial Manager | Mitchell Nissan-Mazda Enterprise / Victor Nissan Selma

Training and certifications

Full-stack immersion | CareerElectricry (2021) Introduction to front-end development | CareerElectricry (2021)

IT skills and languages

MS Office | Basic | nReasonous | Pascal | Cobale | Fortran | Turbo Pascal | | JavaScript Web Server Frameworks | Nodes.js | HTML | CSS | CSS | CSS Flexbox | GitHub | | version control MongoDB | React Native | Express.JS | React | Angular | Postman German, level | English, mother tongue

Rüdesheim am Rhein, 27. September 2022

Terrell C. Lombardi